drumbeatmarketing.net 2017-06-06

# drumBEAT Marketing Privacy Policy

**INTRODUCTION**

drumBEAT Marketing is a Houston-based marketing agency. We care about the online privacy of the visitors of our site. This policy outlines how we collect, use, and protect your information on this site. This notice applies to the drumBEAT Marketing website only and not any other sites that may be linked on our site which may have their own privacy policy. This does not cover our use of information collected through any other means.

**COLLECTED INFORMATION**

In connection with the services we provide, personal information may be asked to be voluntarily given through a contact form or account login. Multiple items of information are included in this form including:

  * Name
  * Company name
  * Email
  * Website
  * Phone number

Your submission of the above information is your consent to our use of the information as outlined in this privacy policy.

In order to provide visitors with a secure experience, our servers record information when you visit our site including URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit. Our site may also collect data on the type of device you are accessing our website on, i.e. a phone, tablet, or computer.

**USES**

We may use personal information to provide the information on the marketing services you’ve requested, to provide customer support, to communicate with you about technical issues, new products and services, and other information or news about our company. Our registration forms always enable you to “opt-out” from receiving e-mail from us unless specifically requested. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our marketing services. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. We process all personal information on our servers in the United States of America.

We offer you options when we ask for personal information, whenever possible. You may decline to provide personal information in our contact forms and/or refuse cookies in your browser. We make reasonable efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct data if it is inaccurate.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are bits of information that are saved by your Internet browser in your hard drive as you browse a website. The drumBEAT site may pull cookies from your computer in order to enhance your user experience.

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**

drumBEAT Marketing does not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age.

**USAGE AND PROTECTION OF INFORMATION**

Personal information collected through our contact form is used for contacting and communicating purposes and to allow us to better respond to an inquiry regarding starting a project with us or learning more about our services. This information is collected in order for us to help you to the best of our abilities and improve user experience on our website.

We do not disclose or sell any personal information collected from website users to a third party without permission from the user.

**OTHER QUESTIONS**

If you have other questions regarding your privacy on this site, please contact us using the information below or using our contact form in the “[Contact](http://www.drumbeatmarketing.net/contact-sales)” page of our website.

drumBEAT Marketing

8582 Katy Freeway, Ste. 221

Houston, TX 77024
